August today in this video we will look at today's
tube and go about some stunning staff in
this my name is program let's
start this video first of all
if we look at the gas market it
shows us at 4000 from the last
because of this crores and court here we have a
consolidated bend during this more
Singapore Nifty 108 click so
looking at this you will again see the 80s
because if the market then you have a very big
playlist later if we talk about futures and
options introduction here minister Jairam
Thakur 30 but if Nifty is above 5300
then you will see today for a minute last Saturday on the
turn of the year
rotis on the network but quarter and
quarter on this side butter but if we look at the
net interest income
in the previous quarter it increased by 1.5 inches
that daily after this Q4 results when
WhatsApp broke its head and beat it
a recipe for dividend payout
in the channel you water to make a cup of tea and 2%
was
[music]
my tablet we rest
This year at 23.53 percent, the company did a tweet experiment.
Don't forget to subscribe to that as well.
You can see more notifications on that as well.
This time we are going to launch Loan SS in the last year.
This match is more unconscious and 150 champions,
so even its taste cannot make you dream,
but in terms of real estate, the revenue has
increased on one side,
but in terms of net profit, the company
launched it in 1969.
Office collection here is 53.67 percent.
When Bigg Boss started its partnership
with Acid, please subscribe to this serum. If you have
not liked and subscribed, then this
side
is removed from its side, hence, in case of only
and data from case, today here call
details can be allocated for investors at 20.5 percent.
After this, from tomorrow, retail
investors will cut this part on its offer for sale.
If we
talk about this, then subscribe my channel today,
they can reset it, you can like and subscribe us on this, so
in the company's drama company, we  Here on Alok
Industries Castron and some companies, if
you all liked this video then
like it and subscribe to the channel,
you will see Abhishek Mukesh's
Kids Wear below
where along with Smart Portfolio
you will get Motivational and Position at Great
in the next video